Hi guys! Today's video is about all these corsets and I'm going to show you that
corsets do make a difference for your outfit. Do you see the difference? But now
have fun with this video! Corset tip number one make sure to put on your
shoes before you put on your corset because otherwise you're stuck. I need
help. I have to declare this video as advertisement because most of these
corsets have been sent to me by corset story so thank you corset story and
there has been an ongoing cooperation I did a lot of pictures for them so I
thought why not do a video as well. They have huge product range so check out
their homepage but if you're already on YouTube go over and check out their
YouTube channel as well because they have a lot of clips featuring the
different corsets, different styles so you can get a good impression. Let's start
with this corset type. It's called Underbust Corset because it ends right
here under the boots and I have quite a few of them because I really like their
fit and I really like that I can wear something under them. So this one is
obviously PVC and this one is satin I have a dressing video with that one well
I have a dressing video with this one so I'm not going to put that on but I
really like the color and the design so what I like about this corset shape is
that you can put it over like dresses and pants and tops so it's very yeah it
has a lot of... I don't know how to say that. Haha. So there are a lot of varieties where you can use an
underbust corset. I'm going to wear this one later when I'm going to talk about
tight lacing so stay tuned. So this one is a underbust version as well. A golden
one and I really like about the corset story corsets that they have different
versions for different body types so I'm wearing the long versions because I have
quite a long upper body and you should check out the product range if you're
like short person under 1 meter 70 or something do take the normal or the
short version but for everyone with a longer upper body I really recommend the
long version under bust corsets and also the long version over bust corsets as
As you can see here, this one came with a satin ribbon for lacing.
This one as well, well basically came with two lacing options, with a satin one and the normal one.
And I switch it up to the normal one.
And I have to say this one may look really good with the satin lacing, but I prefer the other one,
because it is much more easier to lace and it has a better grip so you can lace it tighter.
Speaking about lacing there is a fan lace option available as well at Cosette Stories.
I did own one for a brief amount of time but in my own opinion I was not really satisfied with the
lacing technique. It was really hard to lace it myself and I didn't really think that it did fit
as good as the normal ones but it does look really cool. So bummer. So let's get smaller before we
head over to the overbust ones. This is a waspy whatever it's called. I think the name comes from
the wasp waist. I remember you would say a wasp waist but I have no idea. So this is great for the typical
hourglass look or the wasp look whatever. Just imagine you with a wasp costume. No, I always feel
like a sausage when it's laced too tight. I prefer the underbust corsets because they make a smoother
transition between your waist and your hips. This is a overbust corset although
I think it really is called a corset top, this one at least, because the boning is
a bit more flexible than the steel boning in the others and it is much more
comfortable due to that reason but I like this really much. I ordered it
although I do not like pink but I thought let's try this and I really like
the look of it with the shoulder strap here and I really do not know when I'm
going to wear this outside but I still like it so if you want to order a corset
with some shoulder attachments or shoulders I don't know integrated in
the style make sure that you're not too tall because I tried one of them and due
to my long upper body it was too short and I always like having a hunchback
walking around so it was not comfortable this one is very able so it's good to
wear for me and normal over bust corset
Yeah, that had to happen at least once today.
The normal overbust corset does not have any straps at the shoulders.
So I recently wore this when Fux Toifels visited me.
And as a matter of fact, she did wear the Westby on that day.
It's kind of see-through here at the sides with the mesh.
Kind of like the detail.
and I do like over bust corsets but again I prefer the under bust corsets because
they're more comfortable and in the video I wore my pants over the corset and I think this
is a really cool look like some kind of business look these were my office pants I have to admit
that I was inspired by corset story pictures and videos because they kind of style a lot of their
corsets with the pants over the corset look and I have to say that it turned out better than I
expected and I really like it. I'm going to wear it like that again. Okay let's talk about waist
training. I'm no expert concerning waist training. I am not going to give out any advice but this one
check out the corset story homepage. They have a page dedicated specifically to this subject.
Oh, so the page is called sensible waist training advice. I'm just going to take a look how
Much I can lace this one down and this is like I would wear it normally for night hours
So not too tight
So it's comfortable. I'm just going to check
the circumference now so almost
64 centimeters and
And another corset tip, if you want to lace it down even more just to wait a few minutes
then your body will be prepared if you're going to lace it even tighter.
Barely a centimeter. This is not worth the effort because now it's really uncomfortable.
I'm just not into waist training. I'm just a lazy
because I want to feel comfortable and this is not comfortable.
I admire everyone who does that and as long as it's healthy and I think
it's cool to train your or it's cool to have a small waist but
that's not my cup of tea. Haha switched course it's again because
I'm complaining and this one is somehow more comfortable so I'm going to try again with this
one 66 centimeters so down to 64 centimeters and you have to keep in mind that my waist is not 64
centimeters at the moment but it's smaller because the corset with all the boning and the top
of course add another layer so I would say yeah three to four centimeter less
so I guess my waist is now at 60 61 centimeters and my natural waist is like
66 centimeters and laced it even tighter a solid 63 centimeters that's cool I
I think it's close to the back now.
But now I have to get out of here
because it's not that comfortable.
Although it's okay, it's better than the satin one.
So I have to say even it's the same manufacturer,
the same size, the same long version underbust corset,
there are differences apparently.
And this one is much more comfortable
than the other one somehow, I don't know.
So my natural waist is 66 centimeters.
These are 28 centimeters nearly and I had it closed end to end which makes it 56 centimeters in total
So I think my waist underneath it would have been beneath 60 centimeters
So one last thing if you want to have a toned silhouette and waist but you don't want to wear the corset over your clothes
Just wear it underneath
I
worn this one under a latex catsuit once for photo shooting and I think
it makes editing the picture so much easier because
The figure is just already in shape. So who needs Photoshop?
This is like so cool and it's not even laced that tight
but it makes such a difference and I think that's the origin of
shapewear it shapes the body and is hidden underneath the clothing and I'm
going to enjoy this view in the mirror I'm wishing you a great evening or day
or whenever you watch this video make sure to hit that subscribe button to not
miss out on any of my new videos have a good time see you bye
Thank you.